LE NHA TRANG

FRESHER PHP/LARAVEL

CONTACT

+84 365 767 576

lucas.le3306@gmail.com

https://github.com/lucassle

Ha Noi, Vietnam

SKILLS

- Basic HTML, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Git
- PHP, Laravel
- Quiet good in English
- Basic Japanese
- Basic Design and Edit in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects

EDUCATION

Information Technology

2023 - now

Institution: Hanoi Open University

Back-end Developments

2022 - 2023

<u>Institution: ZendVN Programming Training</u> <u>Center</u>

English Language

2019 - 2021

Institution: Eastern International University

INTERESTS

- Learning more about Information Technology and another languages
- Playing badminton and dancing
- · Reading books
- · Listening to music
- Drawing and Design

PROFILE

I am currently studying Information Technology at Hanoi Open University. Although I am a first-year student, I completed the web programming with PHP/Laravel framework course and did my internship at the ZendVN Programming Training Center, so I hope to have an opportunity to join a new working environment gain experience in a real-world environment.

I can arrange my study time reasonably so that I can work full-time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PHP/Laravel Internship

ZendVN Programming Training Center

12/2023 - 04/2024

- Back-end processing for PHP and Laravel framework.
- · Developing features, building effects and optimizing use for users.
- · Processing, analyzing and designing databases.

Teaching Assistant

Saigon American English

09/2019 - 06/2021

- Consulting and testing new students' English skill proficiency.
- Manage and synthesize students' learning results.
- Guide and support students in lessons with native teachers.

Personal Projects

E-COMMERCE WEBSITE

2023

- Source: https://github.com/lucassle/organice
- Description: Building website functions to sell products based on the database managed by 1 person
- Programming language used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP (Laravel 10), MySQL, docker
- Template used: <u>Ogani-master</u>, <u>AdminLTE</u>